[
    {
        "question": "\u201cSeventy weeks(1) are decreed about your people and your holy city, to finish the transgression, to put an end to sin, and to atone for iniquity, to bring in everlasting righteousness, to seal both vision and prophet, and to anoint a most holy place.(2) Footnotes (1) 9:24 Or *sevens*; also twice in verse 25 and once in verse 26 (2) 9:24 Or *thing*, or *one* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:24",
        "rank": "359"
    },
    {
        "question": "And he shall make a strong covenant with many for one week,(1) and for half of the week he shall put an end to sacrifice and offering. And on the wing of abominations shall come one who makes desolate, until the decreed end is poured out on the desolator.\u201d Footnotes (1) 9:27 Or *seven*; twice in this verse (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:27",
        "rank": "379"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cI saw in the night visions, and behold, with the clouds of heaven there came one like a son of man, and he came to the Ancient of Days and was presented before him. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:13",
        "rank": "506"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cAt that time shall arise Michael, the great prince who has charge of your people. And there shall be a time of trouble, such as never has been since there was a nation till that time. But at that time your people shall be delivered, everyone whose name shall be found written in the book. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 12:1",
        "rank": "530"
    },
    {
        "question": "And many of those who sleep in the dust of the earth shall awake, some to everlasting life, and some to shame and everlasting contempt. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 12:2",
        "rank": "733"
    },
    {
        "question": "And in the days of those kings the God of heaven will set up a kingdom that shall never be destroyed, nor shall the kingdom be left to another people. It shall break in pieces all these kingdoms and bring them to an end, and it shall stand forever, (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:44",
        "rank": "823"
    },
    {
        "question": "and have not obeyed the voice of the LORD our God by walking in his laws, which he set before us by his servants the prophets. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:10",
        "rank": "847"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cAs I looked, thrones were placed, and the Ancient of Days took his seat; his clothing was white as snow, and the hair of his head like pure wool; his throne was fiery flames; its wheels were burning fire. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:9",
        "rank": "1,011"
    },
    {
        "question": "Know therefore and understand that from the going out of the word to restore and build Jerusalem to the coming of an anointed one, a prince, there shall be seven weeks. Then for sixty-two weeks it shall be built again(1) with squares and moat, but in a troubled time. Footnotes (1) 9:25 Or *there shall be seven weeks and sixty-two weeks. It shall be built again* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:25",
        "rank": "1,092"
    },
    {
        "question": "He shall speak words against the Most High, and shall wear out the saints of the Most High, and shall think to change the times and the law; and they shall be given into his hand for a time, times, and half a time. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:25",
        "rank": "1,131"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the king said to them, \u201cI had a dream, and my spirit is troubled to know the dream.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:3",
        "rank": "1,145"
    },
    {
        "question": "But you, Daniel, shut up the words and seal the book, until the time of the end. Many shall run to and fro, and knowledge shall increase.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 12:4",
        "rank": "1,200"
    },
    {
        "question": "All Israel has transgressed your law and turned aside, refusing to obey your voice. And the curse and oath that are written in the Law of Moses the servant of God have been poured out upon us, because we have sinned against him. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:11",
        "rank": "1,286"
    },
    {
        "question": "And after the sixty-two weeks, an anointed one shall be cut off and shall have nothing. And the people of the prince who is to come shall destroy the city and the sanctuary. Its(1) end shall come with a flood, and to the end there shall be war. Desolations are decreed. Footnotes (1) 9:26 Or *His* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:26",
        "rank": "1,305"
    },
    {
        "question": "And he said to me,(1) \u201cFor 2,300 evenings and mornings. Then the sanctuary shall be restored to its rightful state.\u201d Footnotes (1) 8:14 Hebrew; Septuagint, Theodotion, Vulgate *to him* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 8:14",
        "rank": "2,103"
    },
    {
        "question": "And those who are wise shall shine like the brightness of the sky above;(1) and those who turn many to righteousness, like the stars forever and ever. Footnotes (1) 12:3 Hebrew *the expanse*; compare Genesis 1:6\u20138 (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 12:3",
        "rank": "2,257"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the third year of the reign of Jehoiakim king of Judah, Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon came to Jerusalem and besieged it. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:1",
        "rank": "2,258"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the herald proclaimed aloud, \u201cYou are commanded, O peoples, nations, and languages, (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:4",
        "rank": "2,282"
    },
    {
        "question": "I considered the horns, and behold, there came up among them another horn, a little one, before which three of the first horns were plucked up by the roots. And behold, in this horn were eyes like the eyes of a man, and a mouth speaking great things. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:8",
        "rank": "2,326"
    },
    {
        "question": "youths without blemish, of good appearance and skillful in all wisdom, endowed with knowledge, understanding learning, and competent to stand in the king\u2019s palace, and to teach them the literature and language of the Chaldeans. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:4",
        "rank": "2,413"
    },
    {
        "question": "But go your way till the end. And you shall rest and shall stand in your allotted place at the end of the days.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 12:13",
        "rank": "2,433"
    },
    {
        "question": "I saw a dream that made me afraid. As I lay in bed the fancies and the visions of my head alarmed me. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:5",
        "rank": "2,596"
    },
    {
        "question": "And when the multitude is taken away, his heart shall be exalted, and he shall cast down tens of thousands, but he shall not prevail. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:12",
        "rank": "2,792"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the king\u2019s color changed, and his thoughts alarmed him; his limbs gave way, and his knees knocked together. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:6",
        "rank": "2,981"
    },
    {
        "question": "After this I saw in the night visions, and behold, a fourth beast, terrifying and dreadful and exceedingly strong. It had great iron teeth; it devoured and broke in pieces and stamped what was left with its feet. It was different from all the beasts that were before it, and it had ten horns. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:7",
        "rank": "3,058"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then he said to me, \u201cFear not, Daniel, for from the first day that you set your heart to understand and humbled yourself before your God, your words have been heard, and I have come because of your words. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:12",
        "rank": "3,219"
    },
    {
        "question": "The king assigned them a daily portion of the food that the king ate, and of the wine that he drank. They were to be educated for three years, and at the end of that time they were to stand before the king. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:5",
        "rank": "3,318"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the chief of the eunuchs gave them names: Daniel he called Belteshazzar, Hananiah he called Shadrach, Mishael he called Meshach, and Azariah he called Abednego. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:7",
        "rank": "3,395"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the Chaldeans said to the king in Aramaic,(1) \u201cO king, live forever! Tell your servants the dream, and we will show the interpretation.\u201d Footnotes (1) 2:4 The text from this point to the end of chapter 7 is in Aramaic (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:4",
        "rank": "3,440"
    },
    {
        "question": "He has confirmed his words, which he spoke against us and against our rulers who ruled us,(1) by bringing upon us a great calamity. For under the whole heaven there has not been done anything like what has been done against Jerusalem. Footnotes (1) 9:12 Or *our judges who judged us* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:12",
        "rank": "3,469"
    },
    {
        "question": "All the high officials of the kingdom, the prefects and the satraps, the counselors and the governors are agreed that the king should establish an ordinance and enforce an injunction, that whoever makes petition to any god or man for thirty days, except to you, O king, shall be cast into the den of lions. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 6:7",
        "rank": "3,501"
    },
    {
        "question": "And he said to me, \u201cO Daniel, man greatly loved, understand the words that I speak to you, and stand upright, for now I have been sent to you.\u201d And when he had spoken this word to me, I stood up trembling. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:11",
        "rank": "3,537"
    },
    {
        "question": "So I made a decree that all the wise men of Babylon should be brought before me, that they might make known to me the interpretation of the dream. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:6",
        "rank": "3,636"
    },
    {
        "question": "and the chief of the eunuchs said to Daniel, \u201cI fear my lord the king, who assigned your food and your drink; for why should he see that you were in worse condition than the youths who are of your own age? So you would endanger my head with the king.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:10",
        "rank": "3,797"
    },
    {
        "question": "As soon as you hear the sound of the horn, flute, zither, lyre, harp, pipe and all kinds of music, you must fall down and worship the image of gold that King Nebuchadnezzar has set up.",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:5",
        "rank": "3,839"
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniel then said to the guard whom the chief official had appointed over Daniel, Hananiah, Mishael and Azariah",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:11",
        "rank": "3,879"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Then I continued to watch because of the boastful words the horn was speaking. I kept looking until the beast was slain and its body destroyed and thrown into the blazing fire.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:11",
        "rank": "3,898"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cTest your servants for ten days; let us be given vegetables to eat and water to drink. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:12",
        "rank": "3,919"
    },
    {
        "question": "As it is written in the Law of Moses, all this calamity has come upon us; yet we have not entreated the favor of the LORD our God, turning from our iniquities and gaining insight by your truth. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:13",
        "rank": "3,963"
    },
    {
        "question": "And God gave Daniel favor and compassion in the sight of the chief of the eunuchs, (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:9",
        "rank": "3,978"
    },
    {
        "question": "And Daniel was there until the first year of King Cyrus. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:21",
        "rank": "4,038"
    },
    {
        "question": "As for these four youths, God gave them learning and skill in all literature and wisdom, and Daniel had understanding in all visions and dreams. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:17",
        "rank": "4,073"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore the LORD has kept ready the calamity and has brought it upon us, for the LORD our God is righteous in all the works that he has done, and we have not obeyed his voice. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:14",
        "rank": "4,087"
    },
    {
        "question": "The king summoned the enchanters, astrologers and diviners. Then he said to these wise men of Babylon, \"Whoever reads this writing and tells me what it means will be clothed in purple and have a gold chain placed around his neck, and he will be made the third highest ruler in the kingdom.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:7",
        "rank": "4,128"
    },
    {
        "question": "So he listened to them in this matter, and tested them for ten days. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:14",
        "rank": "4,171"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then let our appearance and the appearance of the youths who eat the king\u2019s food be observed by you, and deal with your servants according to what you see.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:13",
        "rank": "4,246"
    },
    {
        "question": "Now, O king, establish the injunction and sign the document, so that it cannot be changed, according to the law of the Medes and the Persians, which cannot be revoked.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 6:8",
        "rank": "4,304"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the magicians, the enchanters, the Chaldeans, and the astrologers came in, and I told them the dream, but they could not make known to me its interpretation. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:7",
        "rank": "4,357"
    },
    {
        "question": "The king answered and said to the Chaldeans, \u201cThe word from me is firm: if you do not make known to me the dream and its interpretation, you shall be torn limb from limb, and your houses shall be laid in ruins. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:5",
        "rank": "4,401"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the end of ten days it was seen that they were better in appearance and fatter in flesh than all the youths who ate the king\u2019s food. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:15",
        "rank": "4,450"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the end of the time, when the king had commanded that they should be brought in, the chief of the eunuchs brought them in before Nebuchadnezzar. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:18",
        "rank": "4,509"
    },
    {
        "question": "But if you show the dream and its interpretation, you shall receive from me gifts and rewards and great honor. Therefore show me the dream and its interpretation.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:6",
        "rank": "4,564"
    },
    {
        "question": "Now therefore, O our God, listen to the prayer of your servant and to his pleas for mercy, and for your own sake, O Lord,(1) make your face to shine upon your sanctuary, which is desolate. Footnotes (1) 9:17 Hebrew *for the Lord\u2019s sake* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:17",
        "rank": "4,578"
    },
    {
        "question": "So the steward took away their food and the wine they were to drink, and gave them vegetables. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:16",
        "rank": "4,583"
    },
    {
        "question": "In every matter of wisdom and understanding about which the king questioned them, he found them ten times better than all the magicians and enchanters in his whole kingdom.",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:20",
        "rank": "4,587"
    },
    {
        "question": "It grew great, even to the host of heaven. And some of the host and some(1) of the stars it threw down to the ground and trampled on them. Footnotes (1) 8:10 Or *host, that is, some* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 8:10",
        "rank": "4,595"
    },
    {
        "question": "For the king of the north shall again raise a multitude, greater than the first. And after some years(1) he shall come on with a great army and abundant supplies. Footnotes (1) 11:13 Hebrew *at the end of the times* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:13",
        "rank": "4,644"
    },
    {
        "question": "and came to make you understand what is to happen to your people in the latter days. For the vision is for days yet to come.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:14",
        "rank": "4,805"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the king spoke with them, and among all of them none was found like Daniel, Hananiah, Mishael, and Azariah. Therefore they stood before the king. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 1:19",
        "rank": "4,823"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then all the king\u2019s wise men came in, but they could not read the writing or make known to the king the interpretation. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:8",
        "rank": "4,831"
    },
    {
        "question": "And a host will be given over to it together with the regular burnt offering because of transgression,(1) and it will throw truth to the ground, and it will act and prosper. Footnotes (1) 8:12 Or *in an act of rebellion* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 8:12",
        "rank": "4,858"
    },
    {
        "question": "They answered a second time and said, \u201cLet the king tell his servants the dream, and we will show its interpretation.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:7",
        "rank": "4,859"
    },
    {
        "question": "And now, O Lord our God, who brought your people out of the land of Egypt with a mighty hand, and have made a name for yourself, as at this day, we have sinned, we have done wickedly. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:15",
        "rank": "4,879"
    },
    {
        "question": "It became great, even as great as the Prince of the host. And the regular burnt offering was taken away from him, and the place of his sanctuary was overthrown. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 8:11",
        "rank": "4,958"
    },
    {
        "question": "At last Daniel came in before me\u2014he who was named Belteshazzar after the name of my god, and in whom is the spirit of the holy gods(1)\u2014and I told him the dream, saying, Footnotes (1) 4:8 Or *Spirit of the holy God*; also verses 9, 18 (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:8",
        "rank": "5,003"
    },
    {
        "question": "So King Darius put the decree in writing.",
        "answer": "Daniel 6:9",
        "rank": "5,107"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then these men went as a group and found Daniel praying and asking God for help.",
        "answer": "Daniel 6:11",
        "rank": "5,132"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"In those times many will rise against the king of the South. Those who are violent among your own people will rebel in fulfillment of the vision, but without success.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:14",
        "rank": "5,190"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lord, in keeping with all your righteous acts, turn away your anger and your wrath from Jerusalem, your city, your holy hill. Our sins and the iniquities of our ancestors have made Jerusalem and your people an object of scorn to all those around us.",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:16",
        "rank": "5,276"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Whoever does not fall down and worship will immediately be thrown into a blazing furnace.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:6",
        "rank": "5,307"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then one who looked like a man touched my lips, and I opened my mouth and began to speak. I said to the one standing before me, \"I am overcome with anguish because of the vision, my lord, and I feel very weak.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:16",
        "rank": "5,437"
    },
    {
        "question": "The queen, hearing the voices of the king and his nobles, came into the banquet hall. \"May the king live forever!\" she said. \"Don't be alarmed! Don't look so pale!\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:10",
        "rank": "5,516"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"How can I, your servant, talk with you, my lord? My strength is gone and I can hardly breathe.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:17",
        "rank": "5,532"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Lord, listen! Lord, forgive! Lord, hear and act! For your sake, my God, do not delay, because your city and your people bear your Name.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:19",
        "rank": "5,552"
    },
    {
        "question": "I said, \"Belteshazzar, chief of the magicians, I know that the spirit of the holy gods is in you, and no mystery is too difficult for you. Here is my dream; interpret it for me.\"",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:9",
        "rank": "5,688"
    },
    {
        "question": "Again the one who looked like a man touched me and gave me strength.",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:18",
        "rank": "5,721"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore at that time certain Chaldeans came forward and maliciously accused the Jews. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:8",
        "rank": "5,778"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then he said, \u201cDo you know why I have come to you? But now I will return to fight against the prince of Persia; and when I go out, behold, the prince of Greece will come. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:20",
        "rank": "5,792"
    },
    {
        "question": "They declared(1) to King Nebuchadnezzar, \u201cO king, live forever! Footnotes (1) 3:9 Aramaic *answered and said*; also verses 24, 26 (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:9",
        "rank": "5,793"
    },
    {
        "question": "In his place shall arise a contemptible person to whom royal majesty has not been given. He shall come in without warning and obtain the kingdom by flatteries. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:21",
        "rank": "5,812"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Chaldeans answered the king and said, \u201cThere is not a man on earth who can meet the king\u2019s demand, for no great and powerful king has asked such a thing of any magician or enchanter or Chaldean. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:10",
        "rank": "5,836"
    },
    {
        "question": "But I will tell you what is inscribed in the book of truth: there is none who contends by my side against these except Michael, your prince. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:21",
        "rank": "5,854"
    },
    {
        "question": "The king answered and said, \u201cI know with certainty that you are trying to gain time, because you see that the word from me is firm\u2014 (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:8",
        "rank": "5,907"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cAs for me, Daniel, my spirit within me(1) was anxious, and the visions of my head alarmed me. Footnotes (1) 7:15 Aramaic *within its sheath* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 7:15",
        "rank": "5,927"
    },
    {
        "question": "O my God, incline your ear and hear. Open your eyes and see our desolations, and the city that is called by your name. For we do not present our pleas before you because of our righteousness, but because of your great mercy. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 9:18",
        "rank": "6,019"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the king of the north shall come and throw up siegeworks and take a well-fortified city. And the forces of the south shall not stand, or even his best troops, for there shall be no strength to stand. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:15",
        "rank": "6,070"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore, as soon as all the peoples heard the sound of the horn, pipe, lyre, trigon, harp, bagpipe, and every kind of music, all the peoples, nations, and languages fell down and worshiped the golden image that King Nebuchadnezzar had set up. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:7",
        "rank": "6,071"
    },
    {
        "question": "The visions of my head as I lay in bed were these: I saw, and behold, a tree in the midst of the earth, and its height was great. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:10",
        "rank": "6,096"
    },
    {
        "question": "if you do not make the dream known to me, there is but one sentence for you. You have agreed to speak lying and corrupt words before me till the times change. Therefore tell me the dream, and I shall know that you can show me its interpretation.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:9",
        "rank": "6,154"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then they came near and said before the king, concerning the injunction, \u201cO king! Did you not sign an injunction, that anyone who makes petition to any god or man within thirty days except to you, O king, shall be cast into the den of lions?\u201d The king answered and said, \u201cThe thing stands fast, according to the law of the Medes and Persians, which cannot be revoked.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 6:12",
        "rank": "6,184"
    },
    {
        "question": "But he who comes against him shall do as he wills, and none shall stand before him. And he shall stand in the glorious land, with destruction in his hand. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:16",
        "rank": "6,228"
    },
    {
        "question": "And I heard a man\u2019s voice between the banks of the Ulai, and it called, \u201cGabriel, make this man understand the vision.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 8:16",
        "rank": "6,324"
    },
    {
        "question": "He shall set his face to come with the strength of his whole kingdom, and he shall bring terms of an agreement and perform them. He shall give him the daughter of women to destroy the kingdom,(1) but it shall not stand or be to his advantage. Footnotes (1) 11:17 Hebrew *her*, or *it* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:17",
        "rank": "6,413"
    },
    {
        "question": "Afterward he shall turn his face to the coastlands and shall capture many of them, but a commander shall put an end to his insolence. Indeed,(1) he shall turn his insolence back upon him. Footnotes (1) 11:18 The meaning of the Hebrew is uncertain (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 11:18",
        "rank": "6,497"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then King Belshazzar was greatly alarmed, and his color changed, and his lords were perplexed. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:9",
        "rank": "6,498"
    },
    {
        "question": "The tree grew and became strong, and its top reached to heaven, and it was visible to the end of the whole earth. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 4:11",
        "rank": "6,627"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is a man in your kingdom in whom is the spirit of the holy gods.(1) In the days of your father, light and understanding and wisdom like the wisdom of the gods were found in him, and King Nebuchadnezzar, your father\u2014your father the king\u2014made him chief of the magicians, enchanters, Chaldeans, and astrologers, Footnotes (1) 5:11 Or *Spirit of the holy God* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 5:11",
        "rank": "6,876"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the king commanded that the magicians, the enchanters, the sorcerers, and the Chaldeans be summoned to tell the king his dreams. So they came in and stood before the king. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 2:2",
        "rank": "7,011"
    },
    {
        "question": "When he had spoken to me according to these words, I turned my face toward the ground and was mute. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 10:15",
        "rank": "7,034"
    },
    {
        "question": "You, O king, have made a decree, that every man who hears the sound of the horn, pipe, lyre, trigon, harp, bagpipe, and every kind of music, shall fall down and worship the golden image. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Daniel 3:10",
        "rank": "7,076"
    }
]